capitalotc.com 2016-05-07

# Privacy Policy • Capital OTC

Updated August 20th 2015 – Welcome to Capital OTC!

Please take a few minutes to read our Privacy Policy, so that you may know if our community is in line with your views and requirements. Please note that if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can write to us and we will answer as soon as possible.

The Capital OTC team respects your privacy and we would like to keep you informed in regards to how the data that you supply and your traffic data is used exactly, so that you know what to expect when accessing our page.

We would like to inform you that all our users are required to be at least 13 years old. IF YOU ARE YOUNGER THAN 13, THEN PLEASE LEAVE OUR PAGE. BY REMAINING ON THE PAGE, YOU GUARANTEE THAT YOU MEET OUR REQUIREMENTS AND YOU WILL BE CONSIDERED FULLY RESPONSABLE IF YOU DO NOT.

This is the current version of the Capital OTC Privacy Policy and this is the only one that you should take into consideration, as previous versions are no longer viable. You are advised to check for updates of this current Privacy Policy, as we reserve our right to make updates, without issuing special notice to you.

IF OUR PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, THEN WE ADVISE YOU TO LEAVE THE CAPITAL OTC PAGE. BY REMAINING ON THE PAGE AND ACCESSING ITS CONTENT, YOU ARE ESSENTIALLY GIVING YOUR FULL CONSENT TO OUR POLICIES.

  1. THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you access the Capital OTC page, we collect two types of information from you. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, so that you may understand what this information is, what we use it for and most importantly, if you feel comfortable with this. IF YOU DO NOT CONSENT TO SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH US, THEN PLEASE LEAVE THE CAPITAL OTC PAGE, AS REMAINING ON THE PAGE WILL BE INTERPRETED AS YOUR FULL CONCENT TO OUR POLICY.

The first type of information that we collect is the data that you personally supply when registering on this website. This data can identify you personally and it includes your full name, e-mail address and phone number and home address, if you have chosen to supply these.

The second type of information is related to the traffic process and we collect it so that we may get a better understanding of how our readers experience our platform and which parts of the content are most successful among readers, so that we might expand on these. Therefore, we will collect data such as your IP address or the amount of time you have spent on specific articles, precisely to better understand if these were interesting enough for you or not.

  2. third party advertisers

The term Third Party Advertisers refers to the companies that we allow to access your traffic data, THAT DOES NOT INCLUDE ANY INFORMATION THAT MAY IDENTIFY YOU PERSONALLY. These Third Party Advertisers will use the information regarding your traffic patterns (the types of pages and content that most often access on our website) in order to provide you with advertisements that you might find to be relevant.

BY CONTINUING YOUR ACTIVITY ON THE CAPITAL OTC PLATFORM, YOU ARE GIVING YOU FULL CONCENT TO THE THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS POLICY.

  3. DATA PROTECTION

The Capital OTC platform takes the responsibility of guarding your information very seriously and we are constantly upgrading our security features and programs, such as antivirus or antimalware programs.

We will continue to maintain a high level of security by utilizing the latest versions of the protection software for your information, but we are unable to fully guarantee the security of your information on a long term, because data breaching software is constantly evolving, thus rendering security software obsolete on a regular basis.

BY CONTINUING YOUR ACTIVITY ON OUR PLATFORM, YOU ARE GIVING YOUR FULL CONSENT TO OUR DATA PROTECTION POLICIES, BUT YOU ARE ALSO ACKNOWLEDGING THE LIMITATIONS OF THIS PROTECTION PROCESS.

  4. CHILDREN

Given the nature of our content, we require all our users to be 13 years of age or older. We reserve our right to verify this fact by making this announcement. THE CONTINUATION OF YOUR ACTIVITY ON THIS PLATFORM WILL BE CONSIDERED YOUR GUARANTEE THAT YOU MEET THIS CRUCIAL REQUIREMENT. WE WILL NOT BE LIABLE IN THE EVENT THAT YOU SUPPLY FALSE INFORMATION ABOUT YOURSELF AND CONTINUE ACCESSING THIS PAGE, IN SPITE OF NOT MEETING THIS REQUIREMENT. ADDITIONALLY, WE DO NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT ANY TYPE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN.

If parents/legal guardians find their children who are under the age of 13 accessing this platform, it is their full responsibility to prohibit their access. If the parents/legal guardians of these children write to us seeking our help, we will gladly comply and remove the underage user from our user database.

  5. SOLE STATEMENT

The Capital OTC community guarantees that this is the only version of a Privacy Policy that we consider active for the time being. No prior version is currently relevant. We reserve our right to update this current version of the Privacy Policy and we will mention the exact date when the update has been made at the beginning of the Privacy Policy page.

It is the full responsibility of the user to stay informed about our latest version of the Privacy Policy, because the latest version is the only one that will be viable.
